import { Question } from "../contestantControls";

export const emmyQuestions: Question[] = [
  {
    id: 121,
    question: "Who published the Cyberpunk 2077 video game?",
    options: ["Gameloft", "CD Projekt RED", "Saber Interactive"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 122,
    question: "When is the original Cyberpunk pen and paper RPG (that Cyberpunk 2077 is based on) set?",
    options: ["2020", "2040", "2060"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 123,
    question: "What is the name of the major expansion to Cyberpunk 2077, released in 2023?",
    options: ["Code Black", "Edgerunners", "Phantom Liberty"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 124,
    question: "Which famous actor plays Johnny Silverhand in the game Cyberpunk 2077?",
    options: ["Keanu Reeves", "Mark Wahlberg", "Dwayne Johnson"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 125,
    question: "What is the maximum level cap in Cyberpunk 2077?",
    options: ["50", "80", "60"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 126,
    question: "What lyrics come after: Another evening and I’ll be sitting reading-inbetween your lines. Because I miss you all the time…?",
    options: ["I really miss you all the time...", "So, get away", "And I’m aware that you were lying in the gutter"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 127,
    question: "In the show Cyberpunk Edgerunners what is Lucy pickpocketing from the backs of peoples necks on the train?",
    options: ["Datashards", "Cyberware", "SD cards"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 128,
    question: "In the Cyberpunk 2077 game what was the name of Johnny Silverhand’s former band called?",
    options: ["Hellbound", "Trident", "Samurai"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 129,
    question: "What is the name of the AI talking pistol that can be found in Cyberpunk 2077?",
    options: ["Skippy", "Bloodhound", "Trigger"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  },
  {
    id: 130,
    question: "What is the name of the project used to store digital personalities, which is also described as a ‘soul prison’ in Cyberpunk 2077?",
    options: ["Heiwa", "Mikoshi", "Cyberspace"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 131,
    question: "What kind of vehicle does the main character in Cyberpunk 2077 normally use?",
    options: ["Hoverboard", "Car", "Motorbike"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 132,
    question: "What year was the TV show Cyberpunk Edgerunners released?",
    options: ["2023", "2022", "2021"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 133,
    question: "What is the name of the iconic implant that David installs in the show Cyberpunk Edgerunners?",
    options: ["Shock Absorber", "Sandevistan", "Kerenzikov"],
    correctAnswer: 1
  },
  {
    id: 134,
    question: "In what country is the developer of Cyberpunk 2077 based?",
    options: ["USA", "France", "Poland"],
    correctAnswer: 2
  },
  {
    id: 135,
    question: "What’s the name of the disease that Johnny Silverhand suffers from in Cyberpunk 2077?",
    options: ["Digital ghost syndrome", "Cyberpsychosis", "Choom"],
    correctAnswer: 0
  }
];